* Features
    
    Key features
    
    * [
        
        How it works
        
        Uncover all features](https://timeular.com/how-it-works/)
    * [
        
        Automated time tracker
        
        Create automatic timesheets](https://timeular.com/automated-time-tracking/)
    * [
        
        PTO tracker
        
        Track all types of leaves](https://timeular.com/leave-tracker/)
    * [
        
        Physical time tracker
        
        Track time with the Tracker](https://timeular.com/tracker/)
    * [
        
        Billable hours tracker
        
        Bill hours accurately](https://timeular.com/bill-accurately/)
    * [
        
        Productivity tracker
        
        Get productivity insights](https://timeular.com/productivity-tracker/)
    
    Product
    
    * [
        
        Integrations and API
        
        Connect Timeular to your favourite tools](https://timeular.com/integrations-and-api/)
    * [
        
        Changelog
        
        See what’s new in the Timeular app](https://timeular.com/changelog/)
    * [
        
        Support center
        
        Get instant support with our comprehensive guides](https://support.timeular.com/en/)
    
    More features

* Solutions
    
    Industry
    
    * [
        
        Enterprise time tracking
        
        Tailor time tracking to your unique business needs](https://timeular.com/enterprise-time-tracking/)
    * [
        
        Team time tracking
        
        Save time on chasing timesheets once and for all](https://timeular.com/timeular-for-teams/)
    * [
        
        Agency time tracking
        
        Maximize time spent on billable work to increase ROI](https://timeular.com/timeular-for-teams/marketing-agencies/)
    
    Download apps
    
    * [
        
        Windows time tracker](https://timeular.com/time-tracking-windows/)
    * [
        
        Mac time tracker](https://timeular.com/time-tracking-mac/)
    * [
        
        Download mobile apps](https://timeular.com/download/)
    
    Success Stories

    [
    
    How an agency increases their revenue by 25% with Timeular](https://timeular.com/success-stories/agency-increases-revenue-with-timeular/)
    
    [
    
    How an IT Team saves 10 hours a week thanks to Timeular](https://timeular.com/success-stories/it/team-saves-10-hours-a-week/)
    
    [
    
    How an IT consultancy became 20% more profitable by using Timeular](https://timeular.com/success-stories/it/how-a-it-consultancy-became-20-more-profitable-by-using-timeular/)
    
* Resources
    
    Free tools

    Templates

    Blog

    [
    
    Timeboxing: Definition, Benefits, and How It Works](https://timeular.com/blog/timeboxing/)
    
    [
    
    Tiger Team Explained: What It Is and How It Helps with Critical Issues](https://timeular.com/blog/tiger-team/)
    
    [
    
    How to Make Time Go Faster at Work: 12 Practical Tips](https://timeular.com/blog/how-make-time-go-faster-work/)

HOLIDAY SALE 30% OFF

Your time matters. Track it with Timeular. All yearly plans are now 30% OFF.

PRIVACY POLICY
==============

1. **General**
    1. Timeular (“we”, “us” or “Timeular”) respects the privacy of its customers (“you”, the “Customer”). The protection of your personal data is of great importance to us and we will use and process such data only in compliance with applicable data protection laws and regulations. To inform you about the personal data we collect, on how and for which purpose this data will be used and processed and about your options with regard to the update or deletion of your personal data collected by us, we developed this Privacy Policy (hereinafter referred to as “Privacy Policy”). Please note that the scope and content of the processing of personal data depend on which of our services and products you access.
    2. Timeular implements reasonable measures to protect your personal data from unauthorized access, destruction, and modification.
2. **Identity and contact details of the controller**
    1. The controller within the meaning of the GDPR responsible for the process of your personal data is Timeular GmbH, an Austrian limited company having its corporate seat in Innsbruck, Austria, and registered in the Austrian commercial register under FN 446345s.
    2. You can contact Timeular by post under Andreas-Hofer-Straße 43, 6020 Innsbruck, Austria or via e-mail under [\[email protected\]](https://timeular.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).
3. **Purpose for the processing of personal data/types of personal data we process/legal basis for the processing of your data**
    1. Processing your order/managing your subscription
        1. If you place an order and/or, in this connection, create a subscription via the Website, we will collect and process personal data which includes your first name, last name, email address, postal address, shipping address, phone number, payment information, VAT number password. Both for the conclusion of the contract as ¡well as its fulfillment it is necessary that you provide such personal data. If you do not provide such data, we cannot close the contract and process your order.
        2. We process your personal data as specified in this section in order to process your orders, manage your payments, send you confirmations of your order, send you notifications of the delivery status and provide other after sales services and customer support. We further use your personal data in order to handle possible complaints or warranty matters.
        3. The processing of your personal data as specified in this section is necessary in order to fulfill contractual agreements and is therefore based on Art 6 para 1 lit b GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation (Directive 95/46/EC)).
    2. Your time tracking account/Use of our software
        1. If you create an account via our Website, our desktop app available at timeular.com/download or our mobile app and use the respective service and our software, we will collect and process personal data which includes your first name, your last name, your e-mail address, your IP-address, your job area, your password, IDs of your devices and your time tracking data. It is necessary that you provide such personal data if you want to use the respective services.
        2. We process your data as specified above in order to manage your account and provide our time tracking services. We further use your personal data in order to provide you with software updates.
        3. The processing of your personal data as specified in this section is based on your consent when you create and use the account (Art 6 para 1 lit a GDPR) and, if applicable, on our obligation to fulfill contractual agreements (Art 6 para 1 lit b GDPR).
        4. We process and analyze pseudonymized data in order to develop and improve our services
    3. Marketing
        1. We will use your name and e-mail address to inform you about new features of our products, ask for your feedback or just to let you know about the latest news regarding Timeular.
        2. The processing of your personal data for marketing purposes is based on your consent (Art 6 para 1 lit a GDPR). You can withdraw your consent for the processing of your data for marketing purposes at any time. You can unsubscribe from receiving commercial messages from us by using the respective link at the bottom of our e-mails containing such commercial messages.
    4. Communication with you
        1. We collect personal data you provide when contacting us (such as your name, e-mail address, postal address or phone number) and will use such data for the purpose of processing your request.
        2. The processing of your personal data as specified in this section is based on our legitimate interest (Art 6 para 1 lit f GDPR).
    5. Comply with legal obligations
        1. We will use your personal data if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with any applicable law, legal process or enforceable request from any competent governmental agency or court.
        2. The processing of your personal data as specified in this section is based on Art 6 para 1 lit c GDPR.
4. **Recipients of your data**
    1. Location of recipient
        1. It occurs that the recipient of your personal data is located outside the European Union and/or processes your data there. The data protection level in other countries may not comply with that of Austria. However, Timeular only transmits your personal data to countries for which the EU Commission has decided that they have an appropriate level of data protection. If this is not the case, we take measures to ensure that all recipients have an adequate data protection level, for which we conclude standard contractual clauses (2010/87/EC and/or 2004/915/EC).
    2. Processing your order
        1. For the purpose of processing your order, we share your personal data with Logsta GmbH, Molkereistraße 6, 2700 Wr. Neustadt, Austria.
    3. Analyzing tools
        1. We use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA (hereinafter referred to as “Google”). Google Analytics uses cookies to analyze the traffic and usage of the Services. The information received by the use of the cookies is transferred to and stored by Google on a server located in the United States. Google will evaluate the information received for the purpose of providing us with analyses and reports, as well as other services that help us to understand how people are using our services. The information collected by Google Analytics’ cookies includes your IP-address. However, as Timeular has activated IP-anonymization, Google shall truncate and thereby anonymize your IP-address. Thus, your IP-address shall be anonymized before being stored on the above-stated server located in the United States. If you wish to refuse the use of Google Analytics, you can do so by selecting the appropriate settings in your browser. Further, to making these settings, in order to prevent that your data is collected and used by Google, you can also download and install the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on available under https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en.
        2. We use Facebook Pixel, an analytics tool provided by Facebook Ireland Ltd, 4 Grand Canal Square, Grand Canal Harbour, D2 Dublin, Ireland. Facebook Pixel allows us to measure conversion rates and to target visitors of our website with advertisements for our products and services in their Facebook – Account.
        3. We use Intercom, analytics and support tool provided by Intercom R&D Unlimited Company, an Irish company with offices at 2nd Floor, Stephen Court, 18-21 St. Stephen’s Green, Dublin 2, Republic of Ireland. Intercom allows us to see your devices operating systems and the actions performed within our apps, in order to provide you better and quicker support. The data will be deleted after you delete your Timeular account.
        4. The processing of your personal data as specified in this section is based on Art 6 para 1 lit f GDPR.
5. **Period for which we store your personal data**
    1. Your personal data will be processed as long as it is necessary to fulfill our contractual or legal obligations and to avert possible liability claims. We ensure that your personal data will be processed in accordance with our privacy policy for the entire period of storage.
    2. For the purpose of direct marketing, your personal data will be stored until you withdraw your consent.
    3. For communication purposes as specified in section 2.4, your personal data will be stored for the event that follow-up-communication occurs for a period of up to twelve months.
6. **Cookies**
    1. Cookies are small text files placed on your device (e.g. mobile device, computer) and stored by your browser. We use cookies in order to improve the security and functionality of our services, to personalize our services and make them more user-friendly. In particular, cookies allow us to (i) distinguish you from other users, which helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our Website or use our software (ii) identify your preferences when customizing content or functionality for you; (iii) confirm you are a registered user and save your log-in details when accessing certain services; (iv) show you advertising, which is relevant to your interests; (v) collect statistics on the use of the our Website and our software. We also use cookies and web beacons to ensure that our mailing tools are working properly.
    2. If you wish to refuse the use of cookies, you can do so by selecting the appropriate settings in your browser. However please note that if you deactivate cookies, certain features of our services may not work properly or will not be accessible to you. You can easily erase cookies from your computer or mobile device via your browser.
    3. The processing of your personal data as specified in this section is based on Art 6 para 1 lit f GDPR.
7. **Your rights regarding the process of your personal data**
    1. Where the processing of your personal data is based on consent, you can at any time withdraw such consent. Upon such notice of withdrawal, we will cease to process your personal data and delete the data collected, except where processing your personal data is lawful even without your consent, like for example in case we have any legal obligation or legitimate interest. Please note, that such a withdrawal does not affect the lawfulness of processing your data based on your consent before the withdrawal.
    2. You have at any time the right to request information about your stored personal data, their origin and recipients and the purpose of data processing. You also have the right to demand rectification, transfer, and, where applicable, to object or restrict the processing or deletion of inaccurate or improperly processed data.
    3. In case of an information or revocation request, you need to file sufficient information to your individualization (at least your first name, surname and e-mail address) and valid evidence that this information refers to you. In these cases, or if you have other questions to our data security please contact our data protection office, whose contact details you will find below.
    4. If you consider that the processing of your personal data infringes applicable data protection law, you can lodge a complaint with the competent supervisory authority. In Austria the competent supervisory authority is the Austrian Data Protection Authority.
8. **Data protection officer**
    1. Timeular has appointed a data protection officer. You can contact our data protection officer, Mitchell Maynard, via e-mail at [\[email protected\]](https://timeular.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).
9. **Google Data**
    1. Timeular’s use and transfer of information received from Google APls to any other app will adhere to [Google API Services User Data Policy](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy), including the Limited Use requirements.
    2. Timeular does not share any Google user data with third-party tools, including AI models.
10. **Android App location data**
    1. The Timeular app requests access to your device’s background location solely to maintain a continuous Bluetooth connection with the Timeular Tracker, even when the app is running in the background. This permission is required for the app to function correctly with the Tracker, but we do not collect, monitor, or store any location data. This functionality is optional and used only for enhancing the app’s Bluetooth capabilities when connecting with the Tracker.
11. **Amendments to this Privacy Policy**
    1. Timeular reserves the right to fully or partially modify this Privacy Policy at any time and – subject to legal requirements – in its sole discretion. Please inform yourself periodically about any modifications of this Privacy Policy. The current version of the Privacy Policy will always be available on our website https://timeular.com/ (the “Website”). Registered Customers will be informed about any such modifications via e-mail.

English

Solutions

Top use cases

Resources

Support & Useful links

General

© 2024 Timeular. All rights reserved.

### Your Privacy

We use cookies to improve your experience on our site and to show you personalized ads. Click 'Accept All' to accept all cookies or 'My Options' to find out more about the use of cookies and to change your cookie preferences.

My Options Accept All

Welcome to Timeular 👋

Login Register

Email\* 

A valid email is required. E.g. [\[email protected\]](https://timeular.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Password\* 

Login

— or —

  Sign in with Google Sign in with Apple  Sign in with Microsoft

Thank you for your interest in SSO, we’re working on this! Meanwhile, you can sign up with an email address and password.

**Forgot password? [Recover](#)**

****

Reset password

Email\* 

A valid email is required. E.g. [\[email protected\]](https://timeular.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Reset password

**Check your email to reset your password.**

Close

Welcome to Timeular 👋

Login Register

 Email\* 

A valid email is required. E.g. [\[email protected\]](https://timeular.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Password\* 

Please use a password with at least 8 characters.

Let's get started By tapping “Let's get started” you agree to the [terms & conditions](https://timeular.com/sa).

— or —

  Sign up with Google Sign up with Apple  Sign up with Microsoft

Thank you for your interest in SSO, we’re working on this! Meanwhile, you can sign up with an email address and password.

****
